Choosing love over money and fame is easy to say, but hard to do.
Without deep, genuine love, it can feel nearly impossible.
So how to love..and how do you express it?
I, never before in my life time
이런 나의 마음 말로
못해서 준비해 봤어 Prime time
Cuz you changin’ me for better
You're the reason for my being
나를 숨 쉬게 하니까
Oh baby It’s all up to you
영원히 나만의 GOAT
사랑의 많은 Paradigm
널 헷갈리게 하지 않아
You know what I need is only you
(Yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh)
사랑이란 확신의 말
거짓 없이 눈 맞춰 봐
Just trust me once baby
I’ll never let you down baby
모두가 원해 (Hey-) 사랑 돈 명예 (Ho-)
But only want you baby baby baby
I only want you baby baby baby
너 없이 빛나는 Fame 나는 원하지 않아
너의 사랑 하나 그거면 돼
Baby baby yeh baby baby yeh
Poppin’, 시간은 금이니까
바삐 너에게 뛰는 심장이 Main topic
I can solve your problem, 그게 나답지
Time together 녹지 않는 나의 Ice cream
가끔 널 잃을까 봐 겁나
그 날이 오면 난 이룬 게 뭘까
Fame, Money, Love 세 개는 많아
Only last one 내가 바란 하나
사랑의 많은 Paradigm
널 헷갈리게 하지 않아
You know what I need is only you
(Yeh yeh yeh yeh yeh)
사랑이란 확신의 말
거짓 없이 눈 맞춰 봐
Just trust me once baby
I’ll never let you down baby
모두가 원해 (Hey-) 사랑 돈 명예 (Ho-)
But only want you baby baby baby
I only want you baby baby baby
너 없이 빛나는 Fame 나는 원하지 않아
너의 사랑 하나 그거면 돼
Baby baby yeh baby baby yeh
사랑을 할 때, I don’t need something
내 마음은 그래, 너에게
너만 있어 주면, I don’t need something
모두가 원해 (Hey-) 사랑 돈 명예 (Ho-)
But only want you baby baby baby
I only want you baby baby baby
너 없이 빛나는 Fame 나는 원하지 않아
너의 사랑 하나 그거면 돼
Baby baby yeh baby baby yeh